

IVÁN LUMBRERAS MARTÍN

RPA DEVELOPER

CONTACT

@

i.martin.desarrollo@gmail.com

C

+34 659 86 56 17

0

Madrid, España

LinkedIn

Portfolio imartin.online





SUMMARY

I am a 20-year-old student, with a great passion for computing, more specifically for the part of AI and neural networks or cybersecurity. Focused on my studies and profession. Efficient and productive. Senior Technician in Multiplatform Application Development and future student of artificial intelligence + robotics engineering.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: B2 - Currently studying C1

EDUCATION

2022 - 2023

Own Title Game development with Unity 3D

CES Juan Pablo II

2022 - 2023

Own Title Competences for employability

CES Juan Pablo II

2021 - 2023

CFGS Multiplatform Application Development

CES Juan Pablo II

2021 - 2022

Javascript Own Title

CES Juan Pablo II

2019 - 2021

CFGM Microcomputer Systems and Networks

Enrique Tierno Galván

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer in Practice

Indra || Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

Computer Technician in Practice

King Juan Carlos Hospital \parallel Abr 2021 - Jun 2021

SKILLS HIGHLIGHTS

Odoo CRM Linux

HTML , CSS, JS y Angular

UIPath

Python

SQL